coachusa.com 2001-12-04

# Coach USA: Motorcoach Tours, Charter Services and Ground Transportation Services

    1. **SECURITY**
    2. **INFORMATION COLLECTION**
    3. **INFORMATION USE**
    4. **DECLINING E-MAIL OFFERS**
    5. **CHILDREN**
    6. **LINKED INTERNET SITES**
    7. **EFFECTIVE DATE AND CHANGES:** ****

Coach USA (“Coach USA,” “We” or “Us”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors to the Coach USA web sites (the “Sites”). While visiting the Sites, We may ask you (“You” or “Your”) to provide information that personally identifies You, including but not limited to, Your E-mail address, name, home address, credit card and billing information (“Personal Information”) for the purpose of interacting with the Sites. To further the protection of Your Personal Information, Coach USA has adopted a set of information management guidelines (outlined below) which serve as the basis for our user and advertiser relationships. These guidelines have been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, guidelines are subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page. Please see the Effective Date stated at the conclusion of this Policy.

| 1. |  SECURITY: When you send confidential personal information to Us on a Coach USA website, We require that a “secure session” first be established using Secure Socket Layer (SSL), Secure Electronic Transaction (SET) protocol when that is fully available. Coach USA maintains reasonable safe guards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the Personal Information that you provide. To the extent Coach USA transfers any Personal Information to third-parties, Coach USA will use reasonable efforts to assure that such third-parties to whom We transfer any Personal Information have knowledge of our Policy and provide sufficient protection of such Personal Information.  
---|---  
2. | 

When You browse any of the Sites, You do so anonymously. Personal Information is generally not gathered by Your accessing and browsing the Sites. Some of our Sites, however, may request that You **voluntarily** supply Us with Personal Information, including Your E-mail address, for purposes such as correspondence, site registration, checking Your bill or investments online, making a purchase, or participating in online surveys.  

Like many other commercial websites, the Sites may utilize a standard technology called a “cookie” to collect information about how our site is used. A “cookie” is a small text file placed on your hard drive by our web page server. These cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, and We do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to determine who you are or your e-mail address. The Sites can only access the information from a cookie sent by the Sites. We cannot access other cookies sent by other web sites or the information contained therein. Additionally, We cannot learn Your email address or any other information about You through the use of a cookie. The only way We would learn such information is if You specifically submit that information to Us, for example, by purchasing a trip through our Sites, by entering a sweepstakes or promotion, by requesting information, etc.  

Coach USA uses cookies to track usage of the Sites and further customize Your experience when You are visiting the Sites. By tracking usage, We can best determine what features of the Site best serve the users. We never give out information to others about individual usage. However, We do provide third parties with aggregate information about our users, such as “2,000 people viewed Your ad today,” as more fully set forth below.  

On those pages of the Sites that do not require registration, You may decline to accept cookies sent by the Sites by selecting an option on Your browser to reject cookies. However, some portions of the Sites may require registration in order to access those areas. In such case, We ask that You register and provide Us with basic information on our registration page. Cookies enable our server to know that You are a registered user; therefore, our registration system requires that You accept the cookies from the Sites. Other sites linked to the Site may also send cookies; however We do not control such activities.   
  
3. | 

If you provide Us with Your E-mail address, or have done so in the past, We may upon occasion send You E-mail offers. We may use information You have given us to, for example, provide a service, ensure proper billing, measure consumer interest in our various services and inform You about the products and services. These offers may be based on information You provided in Your initial transaction with Us, in surveys, from information that may indicate purchasing preferences and lifestyles, as well as information available from external sources such as census bureau data. These E-mail offers will come exclusively from Coach USA or its subsidiaries. 

All offers are carefully developed to ensure that they meet our standards. Our goal is to target offers to people who We believe will find them of value. The lists used to send You product and service offers are developed and managed under strict conditions designed to safeguard the security and privacy of Your Personal Information.

Coach USA does not share personally identifiable information with third parties without permission from the user. Aggregate information may at times be shared with Coach USA partners and other third parties. Aggregate information includes items like demographic information, domain names, and other site traffic information, but does not include personally identifiable information. An example is: X% of subscribers are AOL users, or X% of eligible tickets purchased are e-tickets.  
  
4. | 

Coach USA provides customers with an easy means to decline receiving E-mail offers. Although most customers tell Us they appreciate receiving notice of these carefully designed opportunities, We recognize the importance of providing You with choices.   

When Coach USA first collects information about You, We will offer You the opportunity to “opt-out” of having Your Personal Information shared with parties outside of Coach USA, unless otherwise required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority. Should You not want Coach USA to send You any E-mail or postal mail about our products and services, You also can opt out at the time of registration or information collection. At any time, You may request to discontinue receiving these offers from Us by simply replying to the E-mail and informing Us of Your preferences. All E-mail offers that You receive from Coach USA will inform You of how to decline receiving further E-mail offers. If, at a later date, You choose to have Your name removed from our database, You can do so by sending an E-mail to Coach USA at the following address: [INSERT URL HERE]. Additionally, You may request to view the Personal Information collected about You through Your use of the Sites, by sending an E-mail to Coach USA at the above-noted address.   
  
5. |  CHILDREN: Coach USA does not knowingly solicit data from children or knowingly market to children. Coach USA is concerned about the safety of children and their use of the Internet. Therefore, in accordance with the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, We do not knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. In the event that We receive actual knowledge that We have collected such Personal Information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, We will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical.   
6. |  LINKED INTERNET SITES: You should be aware that other Internet sites to which You hyperlink from the Sites may contain privacy provisions that differ from the provisions herein. Coach USA encourages You to read and understand such privacy policies and terms of use of any Linked Sites accessed by You. If You decide to access such Linked Sites and/or provide any personal information to such Linked Sites, You do so entirely at Your own risk. Coach USA is not responsible for such provisions, and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such provisions.   
7 | **EFFECTIVE DATE AND CHANGES** : This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 29, 2000. Coach USA reserves the right to modify the terms of this Policy at any time and in our sole discretion, by posting a change notice to this page. Your continued use of the Sites following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.  
  |
